archaeologist: n.   考古学家, rest: v.   倚放，放置
Lesson 3. An unknown goddess. Some time ago. An interesting discovery was made by archaeologists
第3课。一个未知的女神。一段时间以前。考古学家提出了一个有趣的发现
Aegean: adj. 爱玲海的, explore: v.   考察，勘探
on the Aegean island of Kea. An American team explored a temple which stands in an ancient
在爱琴海岛的基亚岛上。一支美国团队探索了一座寺庙，该寺庙站在一个古老的地方
promontory: n.   海角, prosperous: adj. （经济上）繁荣的，昌盛的
city on the promontory of Ayrrheni. The city at one time must have been prosperous. For it enjoyed
Ayrrheni海角的城市。曾经曾经繁荣了这个城市。因为它很喜欢
civilization: n.   文明
a high level of civilization. Houses, often three stories high, were built of stone. They had
高水平的文明。房屋通常高三层，是用石头建造的。他们有
drainage: n.   排水
large rooms with beautifully decorated walls. The city was equipped with a drainage system.
大房间，装饰精美的墙壁。该市配备了排水系统。
For a great many clay pipes were found beneath the narrow streets.
在狭窄的街道下面发现了很多粘土管。
archaeologist: n.   考古学家, explore: v.   考察，勘探, worship: n.   祟拜, hip: n.   屁股，臀部
The temple which the archaeologists explored was used as a place of worship from the 15th.
考古学家探索的圣殿被用作15日的礼拜场所。
sacred: adj. 宗教的，神圣的, fragment: n.   碎片
Century BC until Roman times. In the most sacred room of temple, clay fragments of 15 statues
BC世纪直到罗马时代。在最神圣的寺庙房间里，15个雕像的粘土碎片
were found. Each of these represented a goddess and had. At one time,
被发现。这些中的每一个都代表了一个女神。一次，
remains: n.   遗物，遗迹，废墟
been painted, the body of one statue was found among remains dating from the 15th century BC.
被涂漆了，一个雕像的尸体在公元前15世纪的遗体中发现。
remains: n.   遗物，遗迹，废墟
It's missing. Head happened to be among remains of the 5th century BC. This head must have been
缺少。头部恰好是公元前5世纪的遗体。这个头一定是
found in. Classical times and carefully preserved. It was very old and precious even then.
在古典时期发现并精心保存。即使那样，它也很老。
archaeologist: n.   考古学家, fragment: n.   碎片, reconstruct: v.   修复
When the archaeologists reconstructed the fragments, they were amazed to find that the goddess
当考古学家重建碎片时，他们惊讶地发现女神
rest: v.   倚放，放置, hip: n.   屁股，臀部
turned out to be a very modern looking woman. She stood three feet high and her hands rested on her hips.
原来是一个非常现代的女人。她高高三英尺，双手搁在臀部上。
She was wearing a full length skirt which swept the ground. Despite her great age, she was very
她穿着一条横扫地面的全长裙子。尽管她年龄很高，但她非常
archaeologist: n.   考古学家, graceful: adj. 优雅的, identity: n.   身份
graceful indeed. But, so far, the archaeologists have been unable to discover her identity.
确实是优雅的。但是，到目前为止，考古学家一直无法发现她的身份。